Guide to the Communications Workers of America, Local 1180 Records WAG.063
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: General Files, 1956-1986
  - Human Resources Administration: Hours and Scheduling, 1972, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Human Resources Administration: Housing Procedure Meeting, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Human Resources Administration: Income Maintenance Centers: Hours, 1974, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Human Resources Administration: Security Task Force, 1972, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Human Resources Administration: WIN Program, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Human Resources Administration: Workers' Attitude Survey, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Hunter College: Income Maintenance Training Project, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Income Maintenance Centers: CPCU, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Income Maintenance Project, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Income Maintenance Training Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Institute of Municipal management, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Insurance: Group Life, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Judicial Conference, 1966-1974 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Judicial Conference, 1975-1979 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Judicial Conference: Bargaining, 1974-1979 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Labor Organizations: Titles Represented, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Law Department, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Leave Regulations, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Legislative, 1967-1968, 1974-1981 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Legislative Committee, 1976-1980, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Local Officers (List), 1966 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Long Island Federation of Labor, 1977-1981 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Managerial: Confidential, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Medicaid: Training Materials, 1974-1980 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Membership Applications, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Membership Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Meeting Notices, 1969-1976 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Municipal Labor Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Municipal Labor Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Municipal Labor Committee, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Municipal Labor Committee, 1978-1982 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Municipal Labor Committee, 1973-1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Municipal Service Administration, 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Neponsit Home, 1967-1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - New York City Central Labor Council, 1968, 1970-1984 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - New York City Council, CWA, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - New York State Charter Revision Committee, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - New York State Conference of Public Employee Associations, Jan 1973-Mar 1973 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - New York State Conference of Public Employee Associations, Apr 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Occupational Safety and Health, 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining, 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining, 1974-1976, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining: Board of Certification, 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining: Health Advisory Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining: Summary of Digest Decisions, 1968-1975 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Office of Labor Relations, 1964-1969 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Office of Labor Relations, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Office of Labor Relations, 1974-1976, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Office of the Comptroller, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Office of the Mayor, 1964-1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Organizing Drives, 1963-1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Parking Violations Bureau, 1973, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Pensions, 1970-1973 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Police Department, 1964-1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Police department, 1970-1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Port Authority: Employee Relations Panel, 1976-1982 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Port Authority: General Info, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Port Authority: Job Specifics, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Port Authority: Management Memos, 1966-1969, 1978-1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Port Authority: Organizing Campaign, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Port Authority: Organizing Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Port Authority: Personnel Department, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Port Authority: Salaries, 1976-1981 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Public Assistance: New Application Process, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Public Employees Contracts: CWA (Survey), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Public Employees Council, CWA, 1971, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Public Employees Local Presidents' Meetings (CWA District 1), 1977-1980 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Publicity: General, 1964-1976 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Recognition/Representation, 1963-1969 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Retired Members, 1968-1974 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Salary Deferments, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Security: I.M.C.'s, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Security Benefits Fund, 1967-1973 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Security Benefits Fund, 1974-1978 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Security Benefits Fund, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Security Benefits Fund, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Security Benefits Fund, Jan 1981-Jun 1981 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Security Benefits Fund, Jul 1981-Dec 1981 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Security Benefits Fund, Jan 1982-Jun 1982 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Security Benefits Fund, Jul 1982-Dec 1982 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Security Benefits Fund, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Security Benefits Fund, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Security Benefits Fund, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Security Benefits Fund, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Security Benefits Fund, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Security Benefits Fund Handbook, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Security Benefits Fund State Supreme Court Case, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Segal, Martin E., Company, 1974-1975, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Shorthand Reporters/Photostat Operators, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Social Services: Legislation, 1969-1970, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Soundview Center, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Staff, Local 1180, 1965-1984 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Stewards, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Stewards: Lists, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Stewards' Training, 1967, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Summer Hours Dispute, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Taxi and Limousine Commission, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Time Record: A. Cheliotes, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Titles and Codes, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Transfers, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Transit Authority, 1966-1975 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Transportation Administration, 1971-1977 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Tremont Center, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Tri-Partite Panel, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Tri-Partite Panel (Opposition to), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Uniformed Firefighters' Association, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - U.S. Department of Labor: Manpower Administration Grants, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Veterans I.M.C., 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Watkins, Ted, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Welfare Chapter, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Welfare Reform, 1974-1977 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Wyckoff Center: CRT Machines, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Youth Services Agency, 1974, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Series V: Grievances and Arbitration Cases, 1968-1980
  Series V: Grievances and Arbitration Cases, 1968-1980, contains selected arbitrations awards and case files for 1974 and 1976, and grievance files, arranged alphabetically by name (with several additional files of miscellaneous grievances arranged chronologically).
  - Arbitration Award (Board of Education), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Arbitration Case #1-72-215, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Arbitration Case #1-73-102, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Arbitration Case #A-269-72, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Arbitration Case #A-319-73, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Grievances: Department of Social Services, 1968-1972 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Grievances: Department of Social Services, 1973-1976 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Grievances: Miscellaneous, 1968-1972, 1974, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Grievances: A to G, undated (Box 12)
  - Grievances: H to Z, undated (Box 13)
- Series VI: Photographs, circa 1977-1980 (Box Shared Tamiment A005, Folder 1)
  Series VI: Photographs contains five photographs including four color photographs from CWA's Annual Convention in June 1977. There is also one black and white photograph of Arthur Cheliotes and an unidentified man, circa 1980.
- Series VII: Archived Websites, September 2007-ongoing; 2 websites in 2 archived websites.
  Local 1180 is an affiliate of the Communications Workers of America (CWA) and represents public sector and private nonprofit sectors. Public sector employees include administrative and supervisory workers at New York City Mayoral agencies, while others work at Health and Hospitals, Board of Education, Housing Authority, Transit Authority, School Construction Authority, and New York State's Unified Court System. Private sector unions include ALIGN, Amnesty International USA, Books & Rattles/Green Educational Services, Caring Across Generations, Edible Schoolyard NYC, Human Rights First, Human Rights Watch, Javits Center, the National Audubon Society, Nation Institute/Type Media Center, National Domestic Workers Alliance, Open Society Institute, Physicians for Human Rights, Story Corps, Sunrise Movement, The Century Foundation, The Trevor Project, and Tutor Associates. Historically, the union represented the Planned Parenthood of New York City, the ASPCA, and Democracy Now! Productions. The earliest crawls of the website date back to 2007, with news and other materials on the website dating back to 1999. The earliest interation of the website featured news from negotiations and organzing, their political action campaigns, healthcare issues, housing assistance, information on the retiree division, and training and and education services. In 2010, the website redesigned included information on health and retiree benefits, training programs, news, negotiations, their newsletter Communique, and other multimedia. In 2019 the website reeisgned to its current iteration (as of 2023), in addition to previously listed materials on the website, it also featured news and contracts related to the private sector shops that the union represents; special campaigns highlighting union pride; events and meetings; contract negotiations; information on job titles they represent; and salary charts.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
  Accruals
  Websites are accrued semiannually.
  Appraisal
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of cwa1180.org and ftunited.org in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.